(Sheldon:)No. No, this is a slippery slope, Leonard.
See, it starts with a parking space.
Where does it end?
(Sheldon:)It's like my dad always said,
"First they say you can't drink and drive.
Next you can't let your 10-year-old
take the wheel...
(Sheldon:)...while you sleep one off
in the backseat."
(Leonard:)All that story does
is make me feel bad for your mother.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, you're my best friend.
Why don't you ever take my side?
(Leonard:)Because I can never understand
your side!
(Howard:)Give it back.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry,
but could you be more specific?
(Howard:)My Iron Man helmet.
Koothrappali saw you take it. Give it back.
(Sheldon:)Oh, that.
(Sheldon:)Well, see, I wanted it
and you weren't using it.
(Sheldon:)Apparently,
those are the rules we live by now.
Payback, it truly is the B-word, isn't it?
Sheldon, that is a $500
limited-edition collectible...